<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>Firetower Project</title>
    <link>http://firetowerproject.org/</link>
    <description>Recent content on Firetower Project</description>
    <generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator>
    <language>en-us</language>
    <lastBuildDate>Tue, 13 Oct 2020 20:36:16 -0400</lastBuildDate><atom:link href="http://firetowerproject.org/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    <item>
      <title></title>
      <link>http://firetowerproject.org/letter/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 22 Oct 2020 20:30:22 -0400</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://firetowerproject.org/letter/</guid>
      <description>Gentlemen,
United by our common bonds, we write to discuss an opportunity created to provide a great journey. Long ago for some, a recent time for many, we all ran under the banner of black and gold towards one common goal: to achieve the highest glory possible as a cross country team borne out of these treasured and endless mountains trails. There were the close attempts of 7th place in 2001, and 10th in 2000, 2003, and 2007 at Regionals, but not since 1994 has Appalachian cross country reached the pinnacle of NCAA championships.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Mitchell</title>
      <link>http://firetowerproject.org/quote/mitchell/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 13 Oct 2020 20:36:16 -0400</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://firetowerproject.org/quote/mitchell/</guid>
      <description>As members of the team, we all looked to help take the team to a higher level from when we started. The Firetower Project presents us with the opportunity to help perpetuate the program&amp;rsquo;s success after we have graduated.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>1994 ASU Men&#39;s Cross Country NCAA qualifiers</title>
      <link>http://firetowerproject.org/1994/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 13 Oct 2020 20:16:42 -0400</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://firetowerproject.org/1994/</guid>
      <description>In 1994, the ASU Men&amp;rsquo;s cross country team qualified for the NCAA championships, coached by Al Fereshetian.
With alumni support, the goal of the Firetower Project is to produce additional NCAA qualifying teams.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>About Us</title>
      <link>http://firetowerproject.org/whoweare/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 06 Oct 2020 19:53:08 -0400</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://firetowerproject.org/whoweare/</guid>
      <description>We are Appalachian State University Men&amp;rsquo;s Cross Country alumni and supporters.
Contact us at firetowerproject@gmail.com
The Firetower Project was planned and organized by:
 Zack Hollis (2002) Mike Mitchell (2007) Shawn Evans (2002) Brian Deal (2008) James Slagle (2001)  Our era captains are supporting the project by organizing efforts with groups of alumni from different eras. The captains are:
 Franklin Manchester Brian Deal/Mike Mitchell Brandon Hudgins Chris Anderson  We are also supported by the following individuals who have been assisting the Firetower Project:</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Vision</title>
      <link>http://firetowerproject.org/vision/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 05 Oct 2020 21:00:05 -0400</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://firetowerproject.org/vision/</guid>
      <description>Our vision statement is a reflection on the impacts of the Firetower Project when it is achieving its mission.
 It&amp;rsquo;s the Fall of 2025. Excitement has been growing around the AppState men&amp;rsquo;s cross country program. It&amp;rsquo;s been quite a while since the team is headed into the regional meet with a chance at making the NCAA championship.
The team has spent most of the season in the &amp;ldquo;others receiving votes&amp;rdquo; category in the national rankings, and they are pumped and ready to go at the regional meet after winning yet another conference championship two weeks ago, which almost felt like a formality.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Mission</title>
      <link>http://firetowerproject.org/mission/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 01 Oct 2020 15:32:38 -0400</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://firetowerproject.org/mission/</guid>
      <description>In conjunction with the Appalachian State University athletic department and the Yosef Club, The Firetower project is designed to get the AppState men’s cross country team back to NCAA Championships, led by its cross country alumni.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Hothothot</title>
      <link>http://firetowerproject.org/testimonial/hothothot/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 29 Sep 2020 19:32:24 -0400</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://firetowerproject.org/testimonial/hothothot/</guid>
      <description>   </description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Rickroll</title>
      <link>http://firetowerproject.org/testimonial/rickroll/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 29 Sep 2020 19:21:51 -0400</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://firetowerproject.org/testimonial/rickroll/</guid>
      <description>   </description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Hollis</title>
      <link>http://firetowerproject.org/quote/hollis/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 29 Sep 2020 17:17:33 -0400</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://firetowerproject.org/quote/hollis/</guid>
      <description>The time is right to take on the goal of elevating the AppState Men&amp;rsquo;s Cross Country program back to the national stage.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Evans</title>
      <link>http://firetowerproject.org/quote/evans/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 29 Sep 2020 17:16:19 -0400</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://firetowerproject.org/quote/evans/</guid>
      <description>When I heard about the Firetower Project, I knew I had to get involved. It will take many different talents across our wide alumni base to achieve the mission, but I&amp;rsquo;m looking forward to the challenge. Let&amp;rsquo;s do this!</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Slagle</title>
      <link>http://firetowerproject.org/quote/slagle/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 29 Sep 2020 17:14:18 -0400</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://firetowerproject.org/quote/slagle/</guid>
      <description>I recognize the impact that Appalachian State Cross Country has had on my life. I&amp;rsquo;m looking forward to this stalwart opportunity to contribute back to the program with other alumni.</description>
    </item>
    
  </channel>
</rss>
